pearlweb.in 2017-12-23

# Privacy & Cookies Policy - Buy / Sell / Promote / Find Anything

This privacy and cookies policy describes how we handle your personal information. We collect, use, and share personal information to help the PearlWeb work and to keep it safe (details below). In formal terms, PearlWeb, acting itself and through its subsidiaries, is the "data controller" of your personal information.

**Collection**

Information posted on PerlWeb is obviously publicly available. Our servers are located in United States. Therefore, if you choose to provide us with personal information, you are consenting to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers. We collect and store the following personal information: 

• email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information.  
• computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from PearlWeb and Ad data (all through cookies – you can take steps to disable the cookies on your browser although this is likely to affect your ability to use the site).  
• other information, including users IP address and standard web log information.

**Cookies**

We may use cookies to manage our users’ sessions and to store preferences, tracking information, and language selection. Cookies may be used whether you register with us or not. "Cookies" are small text files transferred by a web server to your hard drive and thereafter stored on your computer. The types of information a cookie collects include the date and time you visited, your browsing history, your preferences, and your username. In some instances, our third-party service providers may use cookies on the Website. We cannot control or access cookies used by third- party service providers. This Privacy Policy covers only Cookies used by us, and not any cookies used by third parties. You have the ability to either accept or decline the use of cookies on your computer, whether you are registered with us or not. Typically, you can configure your browser to not accept cookies. However, declining the use of cookies may limit your access to certain features of the Website. For example, you may have difficulty logging in or using certain interactive features of the Website.

**Use**

We use users' personal information to:

• provide our services.  
• resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems.  
• encourage safe trading and enforce our policies.  
• customize users' experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates.  
• communicate marketing and promotional offers to you.  
• Alerts of users intrest  for as described when we collect the information.

**Disclosure**

• All information contained by PearlWeb is treated as strictly confidential and PearlWeb does not and will not disclose or share such confidential information to / with any external organization.   
• The users’ privacy is very important to us. We do not and shall not at any point in time, either sell or rent users’ personal information to third parties without users’ explicit consent.   
• We may be required from time to time to disclose users’ personal information to Governmental or law enforcing agencies or our regulators, but we will only do so under proper authority.  
• PearlWeb also reserves the right to make use of the personal information in any investigation or judicial process relating to fraud on account of such transactions during the period PearlWeb retains such information.   
• We may also disclose personal information to enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other’s rights, or protects anyone’s rights, property or safety.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED BY MOBILE APPLICATIONS**

• Our Services are primarily provided through the Mobile Application. We may collect and use technical data and related information, including but not limited to, technical information about your device, system and application software, and peripherals, that is gathered periodically to facilitate the provision of software updates, product support and other services to you (if any) related to such Mobile Applications.   
• When you use any of our Mobile Applications, the Mobile Application may automatically collect and store some or all of the following information from your mobile device (“Mobile Device Information”), in addition to the Device Information, including without limitation: 

  * Your preferred language and country site (if applicable)
  * The manufacturer, model, Device Unique Id of your mobile device
  * Your mobile operating system
  * The type of mobile internet browsers you are using
  * Data Connection Access (Wifi, 2G, 3G, 4G)
  * Your Geolocation
  * Information about how you interact with the Mobile Application links, such as how many times you use a specific part of the Mobile Application over a given time period, the amount of time you spend using the Mobile Application, how often you use the Mobile Application, actions you take in the Mobile Application and how you engage with the Mobile Application.
  * Information to allow us to personalize the services and content available through the Mobile Application

**Location (On Mobile Application)**

The location data made available on the Application is basic is nature, and meant to provide You the exact listing which relevant your Geo location or area. Without location we couldn't give you exact listing and we know it is waste if your time. So You acknowledge that we get your location details for giving your best listing service. 

**Using Information from us**

You may use personal information gathered from PearlWeb only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam/ phising or collect personal information from someone who hasn't agreed to that.
